bethesdamagazine.com 2006-06-18

# Bethesda Magazine

Privacy Policy

_**For Web Site Visitors**_ Occasionally, visitors to our Web site may be asked to voluntarily supply certain personally identifying information. If you choose to give us your name, email address, postal address, phone number, organization or any other identifying information, unless such information is provided in the course of subscribing to Bethesda Magazine, it will be used only to provide you with products or services you have requested or additional information about bethesdamagazine.com or its affiliates. If you provide identifying information to subscribe to our magazine, please read the policy pertaining to "Magazine Subscribers" below. We will not sell or rent any personally identifying information obtained through this Web site (other than in connection with magazine subscriptions as explained below) to any other organization, and will never willfully disclose any personally identifying information about our audience to any third party without first receiving the user's permission. We do not collect personally identifying information from our visitors, other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.

**_For Bethesda Magazine Print Subscribers_** From time to time we make our subscribers' names and addresses available to reputable companies whose products or services we feel may interest you. Many of our subscribers find this a valuable and time-saving service. If you want us to exclude your name from these mailings, just send a letter to the address below asking us not to release your name to third parties. Include your address label if possible. If not, please include your name, address and phone number. 

**_We can be reached at:  
_**  
Bethesda Magazine  
P.O. Box 15226  
Chevy Chase, MD 20825

Attn: Customer Service
